stablecommunities.org 2009-06-12

# Privacy Policy

#### **NeighborWorks® America Web Site Privacy Policy**

NeighborWorks America respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Web site. We understand that visitors to our Web site may be concerned about the type of information that we collect from visitors and how we treat such information. Please take a moment to read our Web site Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about our Web site Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:

NeighborWorks America  
1325 G Street, N.W., Suite 800  
Washington, D.C. 20005  
Attention: Office of General Counsel  
or e-mail us at [webmaster@nw.org](mailto:webmaster@nw.org)

#### **Our Policy**

NeighborWorks America is committed to protecting the privacy of its online visitors. We will collect no personally-identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) when you visit our site unless you choose to provide that information to us. If you do not want your personally-identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us.

#### **Information Collected and Stored Automatically**

If you do nothing during your visit to our site but browse through the Web site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (e.g., earthlink.net, if you are connecting from an Earthlink account); the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. We collect this information for statistical purposes and sometimes to perform analysis of user behavior in order to measure customer interest in various areas of our Web site and to help make our site more useful to visitors. We will disclose this information to third parties only in aggregate form.

We do not enable "cookies." (A "cookie" is a file placed on your hard drive by a Web site that allows it to monitor your use of the site, usually without your knowledge.)

#### **If You Choose to Send Us Personally-Identifiable Information**

If you choose to to send us personally-identifiable information - as in an e-mail or by filling out a form with your personally-identifiable information and submitting it to us through our Web site – we use that information only to respond to your message or request. This information is only used by those employees who are involved in the operation of this Web site or whose job it is to respond to your message or request. NeighborWorks America never sells any of its lists to third parties. We will only share personally-identifiable information with third parties when (i) the person submitting the information authorizes us to share it; or (ii) we are required to by law. We do not create individual profiles with the information that you provide us.

#### **Site Security**

For Web site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload and change information, or otherwise cause damage.

#### **Linking to Web sites Outside NeighborWorks America**

Our Web site has many links to other sites. When you link to any of these sites, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
